Inventory of the Resistencia Nicaragüense Ejército records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Base San Andrés de Bocay: rosters, lists of wounded personnel, lists of female personnel, lists of children, 1989 (Box-folder 11: 15)
- Base San Andrés de Bocay, Comando Estratégico Nejapa: state of force reports, 1988 (Box-folder 11: 16)
- Base San Andrés de Bocay: weapons assignment lists, 1990 (Box-folder 11: 17)
- Base San Andrés de Bocay: lists of female personnel, lists of children, undated (Box-folder 11: 18)
- Base San Andrés de Bocay, Comando Estratégico Nejapa: list of children, statistical summary of children, 1988 (Box-folder 11: 19)
- Base Las Vegas, Base San Andrés de Bocay: lists of dependents, lists of children, equipment lists, memoranda, organization chart, 1990 (Box-folder 11: 20)
- Base Agateite: rosters, state of force reports, messages, 1982 (Box-folder 11: 21)
- Estado Mayor: manuals of organization, undated (Box-folder 11: 22)
- Estado Mayor, Inspectoria General: manuals of organization, undated (Box-folder 11: 23)
- Estado Mayor: roster, letters, memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 11: 24)
- Estado Mayor Jefatura: rosters, state of force reports, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 11: 25)
- Estado Mayor Equipo de Coordinacion y Apoyo: rosters, undated (Box-folder 11: 26)
- Estado Mayor Equipo de Coordinacion y Apoyo, other Estado Mayor units: rosters. 1990 (Box-folder 11: 27)
- Comando Estratégico, Base Yamales, Sección de Inteligencia, Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas, Cuerpo Consejero Espiritual de Capellanes, other staff units: rosters, state of force reports, weapons assignment lists, memoranda, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 12: 1)
- Comando Estratégico, other staff and line units: rosters, 1989 (Box-folder 12: 2)
- Seguridad del Comando Estratégico, Policía Militar: rosters, weapons assignment lists, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 12: 3)
- Seguridad del Comando Estratégico, Centro de Instrucción Militar: rosters, memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 12: 4)
- Seguridad del Comando Estratégico, miscellaneous units: guard duty assignment lists, messages, miscellany, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12: 5)
- Seguridad el Comando Estratégico, Seguridad del Centro de Suministros: guard duty assignment lists, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 12: 6)
- Seguridad del Comando Estratégico, Cuerpo Médico, miscellaneous units: guard duty assignment lists, rosters, personnel data sheets, messages, miscellany, 1983 (Box-folder 12: 7-8)
- Consejo de Comandantes: logbook journal, state of force report, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 12: 9)
- Commanding officers: biographical data, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 12: 10)
- Policía Militar, Fuerza Aérea: rosters, 1987 (Box-folder 13: 1)
- Policía Militar: rosters, state of force reports, list of female personnel, list of prisoners, 1987 (Box-folder 13: 2)
- Policía Militar, Sección de Contrainteligencia: rosters, 1988 (Box-folder 13: 3)
- Oficina de Finanzas: roster, 1987 (Box-folder 13: 4)
- Oficina de Derechos Humanos: code of conduct, 1987 (Box-folder 13: 5-6)
- Oficina de Asesoría Legal: memorandum, 1986 (Box-folder 13: 7)
- Centro de Suministros: rosters, 1984 (Box-folder 13: 8)
- Centro de Suministros: rosters, memoranda, supply lists, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 13: 9)
- Sub-Centro de Suministros (Aguacate), Sub-Centro de Suministros (Las Vegas), miscellaneous units: rosters, list of personnel infiltrated and returned, memorandum, 1986 (Box-folder 13: 10)
- Sub-Centro de Suministros (Aguacate): rosters, 1987 (Box-folder 13: 11)
- Sub-Centro de Suministros (Corinto), Sub-Centro de Suministros (Aguacate): rosters, state of force report, list of personnel at Centro de Instrucción Militar training, memorandum, 1987 (Box-folder 13: 12)
- Sub-Centro de Suministros (Corinto): state of force report, 1987 (Box-folder 13: 13)
- Grupo de Muleros: rosters, 1986 (Box-folder 13: 14)
- Grupo de Muleros: rosters, 1987 (Box-folder 13: 15)
- Departamento de Carretera: roster, 1985 (Box-folder 13: 16)
- Centro de Suministros (Tegucigalpa), Cuerpo Médico, Base Yamales, Radio 15 de Septiembre, Casa de Tránsito, Sección de Transporte, Oficina de Finanzas, Sección de Contrainteligencia, Fuerza Aérea: rosters, state of force reports, memoranda, lists of wounded personnel, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 13: 17)
- Centro de Suministros (Tegucigalpa): rosters, personnel memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 13: 18)
- Sub-Centro de Suministros (Yamales), Sub-Centro de Suministros (Las Canas): rosters, state of force reports, memoranda, lists of children, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 13: 19)
- Sub-Centro de Suministros (Yamales), Sub-Centro de Suministros (Las Canas): rosters, state of force reports, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 13: 20)
- Sub-Centro de Suministros (Yamales): memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 13: 21)
- Sub-Centro de Suministros (Tipitapa): rosters, 1987 (Box-folder 13: 22)
- Centro de Suministros, Cuerpo Médico, Fuerza Aérea, Fuerza Marina, Sección de Contrainteligencia, Oficina de Finanzas: payroll lists, 1989 (Box-folder 13: 23)
- Seguridad del Centro de Suministros: guard duty assignment lists, 1984 (Box-folder 13: 24)
- Centro de Suministros, Comando Estratégico, Sección de Operaciones Militares, Radio 15 de Septiembre: supply drop logs, communications logs, list of political prisoners, memoranda, lists of human rights officers, rosters, weapons assignment lists, 1987 (Box-folder 13: 25)
- Cuerpo Médico, Sección de Inteligencia: rosters, state of force reports, investigative report, personnel data sheets, supply list, lists of paramedics, lists of patients, lists of children, memoranda, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 14: 1)
- Cuerpo Médico (Batallón Holman): rosters, state of force reports, lists of paramedics, lists of female personnel, lists of children, 1990 (Box-folder 14: 2-3)
- Cuerpo Médico: memorandum, 1987 (Box-folder 14: 4)
- Cuerpo Médico: memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 14: 5)
- Cuerpo Médico, Junta Patriotica Cubana: supply lists, rosters, notes, memoranda, list of paramedics, press release, clipping, miscellany, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 14: 6)
- Clínicas Médicas: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, memoranda, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 15: 1-3)
- Clínicas Médicas: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, 1983 (Box-folder 15: 4)
- Clínicas Médicas: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, 1984 (Box-folder 15: 5-6)
- Clínicas Médicas, Clínicas Dentales: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, reports, 1986 (Box-folder 15: 7-10)
- Clínicas Médicas, Clínicas Dentales: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, 1987 (Box-folder 16: 1)
- Clínicas Médicas, Clínicas Dentales: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, lists of children, 1988 (Box-folder 16: 2)
- Clínicas Dentales, Clínicas Médicas: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, list of paramedic trainees, 1988 (Box-folder 16: 3)
- Clínicas Dentales: memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 16: 4)
- Clínicas Dentales: memoranda, financial records, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 16: 5)
- Clínicas Dentales: memoranda, financial records, 1989 (Box-folder 16: 6-8)
- Clínicas Dentales: memoranda, financial records, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 16: 9)
- Clínicas Dentales: memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 16: 10-11)
- Hospital Aguacate, Hospital Danlí, Hospital Yamales, Clinica Jardín, Centro de Rehabilitación y Aprendizaje Francisco Morazán: rosters, state of force reports, lists of female personnel, lists of children, lists of patients, 1989 (Box-folder 16: 12)
- Hospital Aureliano, Clínicas Dentales: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, 1990 (Box-folder 16: 13-16)
- Hospital Aureliano, Hospital Yamales, Clínicas Dentales: rosters, state of force reports, lists of children, memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 17: 1)
- Hospital Aureliano, Clínicas Dentales, Estado Mayor Equipo de Coordinacion y Apoyo: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, lists of children, 1990 (Box-folder 17: 2)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, rosters, duty assignment lists, memoranda, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 17: 3)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, memorandum, 1982 December-1983 January (Box-folder 17: 4)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, 1983 September (Box-folder 17: 5)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, 1983 September-October (Box-folder 17: 6)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, 1983 October (Box-folder 17: 7)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, roster, memorandum, 1983 (mainly 1983 October-November) (Box-folder 17: 8)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 17: 9)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, 1984 January (Box-folder 17: 10)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, roster, 1984 January-February (Box-folder 17: 11)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, miscellany, 1984 (mainly 1984 March) (Box-folder 17: 12)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, 1984 February-March (Box-folder 17: 13)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, rosters, 1984 March (Box-folder 17: 14)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, rosters, 1984 March-April (Box-folder 17: 15)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, state of force report, memorandum, 1984 (mainly 1984 April) (Box-folder 17: 16)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, memoranda, 1984 April-May (Box-folder 17: 17)
- Hospital Danlí: patient records, 1984 April-May (Box-folder 17: 18)
- Centro de Rehabilitación y Aprendizaje Francisco Morazán (Proyecto Rancho Grande): rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, lists of female personnel, lists of children, 1990 (Box-folder 17: 19-20)
- Centro de Rehabilitación y Aprendizaje Francisco Morazán, Hospital Danlí, Batallón de Comunicaciones Militares, Centro de Suministros: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, lists of female personnel, lists of children, memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 17: 21)
- Centro de Rehabilitación y Aprendizaje Francisco Morazán: lists of patients, undated (Box-folder 17: 22)
- Centro de Rehabilitación y Aprendizaje Francisco Morazán: financial records, manifesto, 1988 (Box-folder 17: 23)
- Centro de Rehabilitación y Aprendizaje Francisco Morazán, Americas Watch: manual, rules, plans, reports, political asylum application, 1989 (Box-folder 17: 24)
- Hospital Yamales, Clínicas Médicas, Clínicas Dentales: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, lists of paramedics, lists of female personnel, lists of children, 1989 (Box-folder 18: 1)
- Clinica Jardín, Hospital Aguacate, Hospital Danlí: rosters, state of force reports, lists of patients, 1987 (Box-folder 18: 2)
- Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas: roster, 1990 (Box-folder 18: 3)
- Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas: messages, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18: 4)
- Cuerpo Consejeros Espiritual de Capellanes: roster, reports, 1989 (Box-folder 18: 5)
- Cuerpo Consejeros Espiritual de Capellanes, Sección de Personal: roster, memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18: 6)
- Cuerpo Consejeros Espiritual de Capellanes: reports, bulletins, 1990 (Box-folder 18: 7-8)
- Cuerpo Consejeros Espiritual de Capellanes: marriage licenses, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18: 9)
- Cuerpo Consejeros Espiritual de Capellanes: marriage licenses, 1990 (Box-folder 18: 10)
- Centro de Entrenamiento Comando: rosters, memoranda, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 18: 11)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: rosters, state of force reports, list of children, messages, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 18: 12)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: roster, 1989 (Box-folder 18: 13)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: rosters, state of force reports, lists of children, 1989 (Box-folder 18: 14-15)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: rosters, state of force reports, 1990 (Box-folder 18: 16-17)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: basic infantry course, leadership course, commander course, artillery course schedules, rosters, state of force reports, memoranda, personnel data sheet, 1985 (Box-folder 18: 18)
- Centro de Entrenamiento Comando: leadership course, paramedic course, psychological warfare course, parachutist course, artillery course, intelligence course rosters, memoranda, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 19: 1)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: leadership course rosters, 1989 (Box-folder 19: 2)
- Centro de Entrenamiento Comando: leadership course instructional material, identification document, code key, miscellany, 1983 (Box-folder 19: 3)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: demolitions course roster, 1986 (Box-folder 19: 4)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: intelligence course roster, 1989 (Box-folder 19: 5)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: missile course rosters, miscellany, 1987 (Box-folder 19: 6)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: missile course messages, memoranda, 1988 (Box-folder 19: 7)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: paramedic course data sheets for trainees, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 19: 8)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: paramedic course, missile course, psychological warfare course, demolitions course, accounting course, mobile instructor course, sniper course, cook course, guerrilla warfare course, parachutist course, commander course rosters, state of force reports, schedules, memoranda, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 19: 9)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: paramedic course rosters, 1989 (Box-folder 19: 10)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: paramedic course rosters, 1990 (Box-folder 19: 11)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: administrative course rosters, 1990 (Box-folder 19: 12)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: artillery course rosters, memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 19: 13)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: guerrilla warfare course instructional material, undated (Box-folder 19: 14)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: radio operator course rosters, memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 19: 15)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: instructional materials, organizational outlines, 1988 (Box-folder 19: 16)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: course completion certificates, 1986 (Box-folder 19: 17-18)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: course completion certificate, 1989 (Box-folder 19: 19)
- Centro de Instrucción Militar: course completion certificate, undated (Box-folder 19: 20)
- Agency for International Development, Centro de Capacitacion Administrativo Rafaela Herrera, Centro de Capacitacion Administrativo Batallón Santiago Meza: literacy course, health course, academic course, vocational training course rosters, memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 19: 21)
- Cuerpo de Transmisiones, Comando Estratégico, Sección de Transporte, Sección de Inteligencia, Oficina de Asesoría Legal, Policía Militar, Fuerza Aérea, Unidad de Artillería, C.R. Larry McDonald, C.R. Jorge Salazar #1, F.T. Jose Adán Sevilla, Base San Andrés de Bocay: rosters, state of force reports, memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 20: 1)
- Cuerpo de Transmisiones: rosters, miscellany, 1987 (Box-folder 20: 2)
- Cuerpo de Transmisiones: rosters, state of force reports, lists of aspirant radio operators, memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 20: 3)
- Servicios Técnicos, Comunicaciones y Ingeniería: rosters, memorandum, 1989 (Box-folder 20: 4)
- Sección de Transporte: rosters, state of force reports, 1990 (Box-folder 20: 5)
- Batallón Apoyo Auxiliar: rosters, state of force reports, list of personnel infiltrated and returned, memoranda, miscellany, 1989 (Box-folder 20: 6)
- Batallón Apoyo Auxiliar: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1990 (Box-folder 20: 7)
- Batallón Apoyo Auxiliar: roster, undated (Box-folder 20: 8)
- Batallón Apoyo Auxiliar: weapons assignment lists, 1990 (Box-folder 20: 9)
- Puesto de Mando Avanzado: rosters, weapons assignment lists, 1987 (Box-folder 20: 10)
- Personnel captured: lists, reports, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 20: 11)
- Personnel captured: lists, reports, personnel data sheet, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 20: 12)
- Personnel captured: lists, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 20: 13)
- Personnel captured: letter, 1989 (Box-folder 20: 14)
- Sandinistas captured, Sandinistas killed: lists, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 20: 15)
- Personnel killed: biographical data, reports, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 20: 16)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel, enemy casualties: summaries, 1984 (Box-folder 20: 17)
- Personnel killed, Sección de Personal: lists, reports, regulations, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 20: 18)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel: lists, summaries, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 21: 1)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel, ex-Guardia Nacional personnel killed, enemy casualties: lists, summaries, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 21: 2)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel, ex-Guardia Nacional personnel killed, Centro de Instrucción Militar training graduates killed: lists, summaries, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 21: 3)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel: lists, summaries, reports, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 21: 4-5)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel, enemy casualties: summaries, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 21: 6)
- Personnel killed: lists, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 21: 7)
- Personnel killed, personnel captured, human rights violations: lists, report, 1989 (Box-folder 21: 8)
- Personnel killed: lists, blank forms, 1989 (Box-folder 21: 9)
- Personnel killed, Sandinistas killed: lists, blank forms, 1989 (Box-folder 21: 10)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel: lists, reports, 1989 (Box-folder 21: 11)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel, personnel captured, Sandinista human rights violations: lists, summaries, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 21: 12)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel, personnel captured, deserters, ex-Sandinistas integrated, Sandinista human rights violations: lists, summaries, reports, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 21: 13)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel: lists, 1989 (Box-folder 21: 14)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel, personnel captured, deserters, enemy casualties, ex-Sandinistas integrated: summaries, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 21: 15)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel: lists, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 1-2)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel: lists, summaries, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 3-4)
- Personnel killed: reports, lists, 1989 (Box-folder 22: 5)
- Personnel killed: reports, lists, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 6)
- Personnel killed, wounded personnel, deserters: reports, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 7)
- Wounded personnel, personnel unfit for duty, defectors to Sandinistas: lists, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 22: 8)
- Wounded personnel: lists, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 22: 9-10)
- Wounded personnel, personnel unfit for duty: lists, messages, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 11-13)
- Wounded personnel, personnel unfit for duty: lists, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 14)
- Deserters, beneficiaries: lists, personnel data sheets, reports, messages, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 22: 15)
- Deserters: lists, reports, messages, 1986 (Box-folder 22: 16)
- Deserters: lists, reports, messages, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 22: 17)
- Deserters, female personnel: lists, messages, 1987 (Box-folder 22: 18)
- Defectors to Sandinistas: lists, messages, clippings, 1988 (Box-folder 22: 19)
- Defectors to Sandinistas: lists, reports, messages, 1989 (Box-folder 22: 20)
- Deserters: lists, reports, messages, 1989 (Box-folder 22: 21)
- Deserters, personnel captured: summaries, lists, 1989 (Box-folder 22: 22)
- Deserters: messages, 1987 (Box-folder 22: 23-24)
- Deserters: messages, 1988 (Box-folder 22: 25)
- Deserters: messages, lists, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 26)
- Enemy casualties: summaries, lists, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 23: 1)
- Enemy casualties: summaries, 1988 (Box-folder 23: 2)
- Discharged personnel: lists, memoranda, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 23: 3)
- Discharged personnel, personnel killed, personnel expelled: lists, memoranda, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 23: 4)
- Discharges, other personnel actions: certifications, memoranda, miscellaneous personnel lists, miscellany, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 23: 5)
- Discharge: certification, 1984 (Box-folder 23: 6)
- Discharges, other personnel actions, humanitarian aid: certifications, authorizations, personnel memoranda, miscellaneous personnel lists, miscellany, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 23: 7)
- Discharges, other personnel actions: certifications, memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 23: 8)
- CLOSED (Box-folder 23: 9-10)
- Discharges: certifications, 1989 (Box-folder 23: 11)
- Discharges, other personnel actions: certifications, memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 23: 12)
- Discharges: memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 23: 13)
- Discharges, other personnel actions: certifications, memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 23: 14)
- Undesirable discharges: list, 1982 (Box-folder 23: 15)
- Resignations: letters, memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 23: 16)
- Resignation: letter, 1990 (Box-folder 23: 17)
- Appointments, discharges, transfers: memoranda, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 23: 18)
- Appointments: memoranda, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 23: 19)
- Appointments, other personnel actions: memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 23: 20)
- Appointments: memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 23: 21)
- Transfers, other personnel actions: memoranda, lists, miscellany, 1987 (Box-folder 23: 22)
- Transfers, other personnel actions: memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 23: 23)
- Transfers, other personnel actions: memoranda, 1988 (Box-folder 23: 24)
- CLOSED (Box-folder 23: 25)
- Transfers, other personnel actions, human rights violations: memoranda, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 24: 1)
- Transfers, other personnel actions: memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 24: 2)
- Transfers: memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 3)
- Personnel actions: authorization, 1984 (Box-folder 24: 4)
- Personnel actions: authorizations, memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 5-6)
- Personnel actions: requests, memoranda, requisition, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 24: 7)
- Personnel actions: requests, memoranda, blank forms, miscellany, 1987 (Box-folder 24: 8)
- Personnel actions: requests, memoranda, requisition, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 24: 9)
- Personnel actions: request memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 10)
- Personnel actions: request, undated (Box-folder 24: 11)
- Personnel actions, equipment: memoranda, requests, lists, telegram, 1956-1983 (Box-folder 24: 12)
- Personnel actions: memorandum, clipping, 1982 (Box-folder 24: 13)
- Personnel actions, equipment: memoranda, lists, notes, miscellany, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 24: 14)
- Personnel actions, Miscellany: memoranda, news dispatches, press release, state of force report, code keys, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 24: 15)
- Personnel actions: memoranda, miscellany, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 24: 16)
- Personnel actions: memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 24: 17-19)
- Personnel actions, Miscellany: memoranda, identification documents, notes, miscellany, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 24: 20)
- Personnel actions, contacts in Honduras: memoranda, communications with Honduran officials, 1989 (Box-folder 24: 21)
- Personnel actions: memoranda, reports, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 24: 22)
- Personnel actions: memoranda, reports, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 23-24)
- Personnel actions, Miscellany: memoranda, letters, miscellany, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 25)
- Personnel actions: recommendations, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 26)
- Prisoners, wounded personnel: lists, memoranda, miscellany, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 24: 27)
- Prisoners: lists, 1985 (Box-folder 24: 28)
- Prisoners: lists, memoranda, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 24: 29)
- Prisoners: list, 1988 (Box-folder 24: 30)
- Prisoners: lists, memoranda, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 24: 31)
- Prisoners: lists, 1989 (Box-folder 24: 32)
- Prisoners: lists, memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 24: 33)
- Prisoners: lists, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 34)
- CLOSED (Box-folder 25)
- Fiscalía Militar: semi-annual report, 1988 (Box-folder 26: 1)
- CLOSED (Box-folder 26: 2)
- Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas, Sección de Inteligencia, Fiscalía Militar, Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: investigative reports, human rights reports, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 26: 3)
- Seguridad del Estado Mayor, Sección de Personal: memoranda, lists, interrogation reports, miscellany, 1990 (Box-folder 26: 4)
- Arbolito case: report, 1987 (Box-folder 26: 5)
- Carmen case: reports, memoranda, letters (Sección de Personal), 1989-1990 (Box-folder 26: 6)
- Dimas case: memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 26: 7)
- Edgar case: memoranda (Sección de Personal), 1989 (Box-folder 26: 8)
- Pata de Fierro case: memorandum, 1986 (Box-folder 26: 9)
- Raul Arroliga case: memorandum, undated (Box-folder 26: 10)
- Tiro al Blanco case: tribunal proceedings, memoranda, 1986 (Box-folder 26: 11)